A Guide to the The Road Company Records, 1972-1998
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Tennessee Arts Commission: Special Projects, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-59)
- ETSU Theater Requests, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-60)
- Plays in Process Nominations, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-61)
- SAF Proposal, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-62)
- Box Office Statements, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-63)
- National Endowment for the Arts, Expansion Arts Program, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-64)
- Southern Arts Federation (SAF) Program, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-65)
- National Endowment for the Arts—Roots Tour, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-66)
- Tennessee Arts Commission Financial Papers, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-67)
- Monthly Income and Balance Sheets, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 10-1)
- Financial Statements, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 10-2)
- Miscellaneous, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 10-3)
- Pictures from "Echoes and Postcards," 1985-1986. (Box-folder 10-4)
- Thank you letters to Business Contributors, 1985-1988. (Box-folder 10-5)
- Kenny Raskins, 1986. (Box-folder 10-6)
- SAF Information, 1986. (Box-folder 10-7)
- Road Company Retreat, 1986. (Box-folder 10-8)
- Interest Letters and Contacts, 1986. (Box-folder 10-9)
- Press Packet for "Echoes," 1986. (Box-folder 10-10)
- HUB Information, 1986. (Box-folder 10-11)
- Fundraising Letter, 1986. (Box-folder 10-12)
- Greater Tuna Lists, 1986. (Box-folder 10-13)
- Road Company Productions, 1986. (Box-folder 10-14)
- Letters, 1986. (Box-folder 10-15)
- Miscellaneous, 1986. (Box-folder 10-16)
- Tennessee Arts Commission—Policies, 1986. (Box-folder 10-17)
- Interested Sponsors, 1986. (Box-folder 10-18)
- "Echoes" Interest, 1986. (Box-folder 10-19)
- Sponsor Negotiations Records, 1986. (Box-folder 10-20)
- Negative Responses, 1986. (Box-folder 10-21)
- Contracts (Fall Tour), 1986. (Box-folder 10-22)
- "Greater Tuna"—Related to David Keith, 1986. (Box-folder 10-23)
- Pictures from the Valentine's Day Dance, 1986. (Box-folder 10-24)
- Financial Statements, 1986. (Box-folder 10-25)
- Fall Tour Evaluations, 1986. (Box-folder 10-26)
- Echoes—One act, 1986. (Box-folder 10-27)
- Echoes and Postcards, 1986. (Box-folder 10-28)
- Echoes and Postcards Miscellaneous. 1986. (Box-folder 10-29)
- Roadside Public Relations, 1986. (Box-folder 10-30)
- Art Show Receipts, 1986. (Box-folder 10-31)
- Publication Request of "Blind Desire" by Grand Valley State College, 1986. (Box-folder 10-32)
- Samuel French, Inc: Royalties for Greater Tuna, 1986. (Box-folder 10-33)
- Vickishell, 1986. (Box-folder 10-34)
- IATSE, 1986. (Box-folder 10-35)
- Roots and ETSU, 1986. (Box-folder 10-36)
- Roots Fed Apt, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-37)
- Government Budget, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-38)
- Art Auction Information, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-39)
- Art Auction, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-40)
- The Road Company Arts and Theater, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-41)
- Tax forms, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-42)
- Roots Tour Support, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-43)
- NEA and Roots, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-44)
- Audit, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-45)
- Income Tax Report, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-46)
- Subscriptions, 1986-1987. (Box-folder 10-47)
- Letters of Support, 1986-1989. (Box-folder 10-48)
- Reservation Records, 1986-1989. (Box-folder 10-49)
- Letters of Support and Praise, 1986-1992. (Box-folder 10-50)
- Art Auction Thank You Notes, 1987. (Box-folder 11-1)
- Bucknell University, 1987. (Box-folder 11-2)
- Christmas Pictures, 1987. (Box-folder 11-3)
- Tartuffe Photos, 1987. (Box-folder 11-4)
- Lilly Baker Photos, 1987. (Box-folder 11-5)
- Tour Information, 1987. (Box-folder 11-6)
- First Tennessee National Corporation Contributions Program Application, 1987. (Box-folder 11-7)
- Plans for Reception in honor of Business Contributors, 1987. (Box-folder 11-8)
- Audit, 1987. (Box-folder 11-9)
- NEXUS: Interdisciplinary Arts Fellowship Program, 1987. (Box-folder 11-10)
- Spring Tour Evaluations, 1987. (Box-folder 11-11)
- Contracts (Spring Tour), 1987. (Box-folder 11-12)
- Survey Example, 1987. (Box-folder 11-13)
- Tax Exempt Forms for Shopping, 1987. (Box-folder 11-14)
- TPAC, 1987. (Box-folder 11-15)
- Possible Bookings, 1987. (Box-folder 11-16)
- PTA Council, 1987. (Box-folder 11-17)
- Public Relations Lists, 1987. (Box-folder 11-18)
- Correspondence (Thank you letters), 1987. (Box-folder 11-19)
- Anonymous Donor, 1987. (Box-folder 11-20)
- Royalties for Plays by Ken Jenkins, 1987. (Box-folder 11-21)
- Royalties for "The Loveliest Afternoon of the Year," 1987. (Box-folder 11-22)
- Service Organizations, 1987. (Box-folder 11-23)
- American Directors Institute, 1987. (Box-folder 11-24)
- PTA Roots, 1987. (Box-folder 11-25)
- Medical School Mailing Lists, 1987-1988. (Box-folder 11-26)
- "Echoes" Contracts, 1987-1988. (Box-folder 11-27)
- NEA and Roots, 1987-1988. (Box-folder 11-28)
- Miscellaneous, 1987-1988. (Box-folder 11-29)
- Business Fundraising Campaign, 1987-1988. (Box-folder 11-30)
- Miscellaneous Business Notes, 1987-1988. (Box-folder 11-31)
- Daytrips, 1988. (Box-folder 11-32)
- Daytrips—7 stages, 1988. (Box-folder 11-33)
- Samuel French, Inc.: Royalties for "Happy Days," 1988. (Box-folder 11-34)
- Lime Kiln Arts, 1988. (Box-folder 11-35)
- South Africa, 1988. (Box-folder 11-36)
- Shawn's Show, 1988. (Box-folder 11-37)
- Contribution Request to United Telephone System, 1988. (Box-folder 11-38)
- Grant from General Mills Foundation, 1988. (Box-folder 11-39)
- Business Fundraiser Campaign, 1988. (Box-folder 11-40)
- Celeste Miller, 1988. (Box-folder 11-41)
- Student Letters on "Echoes and Postcards," 1988. (Box-folder 11-42)
- Reviews for "Bernarda Alba and Garcia Lorca-A Portrait in White." 1988. (Box-folder 11-43)
- Sheraton Contracts, 1988. (Box-folder 11-44)
- THC Grant, 1988. (Box-folder 11-45)
- Road Company Golf Tournament, 1988. (Box-folder 11-46)
- Brochure, 1988. (Box-folder 11-47)
- Virex Program Information, 1988. (Box-folder 11-48)
- Subscription Sales Information, 1988. (Box-folder 11-49)
- Bloomsburg Theater Ensemble, 1988. (Box-folder 11-50)
- Fundraising Campaign, 1988. (Box-folder 11-51)
- "Urban Centers" Information, 1988. (Box-folder 11-52)
- Member's Hard Copies, 1988. (Box-folder 11-53)
- Art Auction, 1988. (Box-folder 11-54)
- Art Auction Artists, 1988. (Box-folder 11-55)
- Membership Directory, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 11-56)
- Echoes Contracts, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 11-57)
- Subscriptions and Donations, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 11-58)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 11-59)
- Patron Call Response Sheets, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 11-60)
- Program Advertisements, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 11-61)
- Plays in Process: Day trips, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 11-62)
- Check Request Forms, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-1)
- Audit, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-2)
- Johnson City schools, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-3)
- Expansion Arts, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-4)
- NEA theater 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-5)
- Season subscription, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-6)
- SAF, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-7)
- Roots, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-8)
- TAC, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-9)
- The Road Company Rag, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-10)
- Box Office, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-11)
- Pigs, 1988-1989. (Box-folder 12-12)
- NEA Arts, 1988-1992. (Box-folder 12-13)
- NEA Theater, 1988-1993. (Box-folder 12-14)
- NEA Arts, 1988-1993. (Box-folder 12-15)
- Contracts and Technical Information, 1989. (Box-folder 12-16)
- Fall contracts, 1989. (Box-folder 12-17)
- Miracle photos, 1989. (Box-folder 12-18)
- Pigs photos, 1989. (Box-folder 12-19)
- Daytrip photos, 1989. (Box-folder 12-20)
- Business Contributions, 1989. (Box-folder 12-21)
- Alan Bryce—Director, 1989. (Box-folder 12-22)
- Appalachian Community Fund: Software Donation Application, 1989. (Box-folder 12-23)
- Apple Computer Product Papers, 1989. (Box-folder 12-24)
- Various Plays by Mary Alice Mark, 1989. (Box-folder 12-25)
- Fall Interest Sheets, 1989. (Box-folder 12-26)
- Correspondence—Thank you letters, 1989. (Box-folder 12-27)
- Touring Proposals, 1989. (Box-folder 12-28)
- Bob's Business Campaign Contracts, 1989. (Box-folder 12-29)
- Samuel French, Inc: Royalties for "Voice of the Prairie," 1989. (Box-folder 12-30)
- U.S. Senator Alliance, 1989. (Box-folder 12-31)
- Post Production, 1989. (Box-folder 12-32)
- NEA/Rockefeller"New Forms, 1989. (Box-folder 12-33)
- The Miracle Play, 1989. (Box-folder 12-34)
- Art Auction Artist Registration, 1989. (Box-folder 12-35)
- Art Auction, 1989. (Box-folder 12-36)
- The Road Company Brochures, 1989. (Box-folder 12-37)
- Carleen Claybaker's House, 1989. (Box-folder 12-38)
- Proposals for Humanities Association, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 12-39)
- Budget, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 12-40)
- Hub Holes, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 12-41)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Finanacial Papers for Grant, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-1)
- Long Range Plans, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-2)
- Tennessee Children Youth, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-3)
- National Endowmwnt for the Arts: Expansion Arts Program, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-4)
- Program Advertisements, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-5)
- Patrol Call Responses, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-6)
- The Road Company Rag, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-7)
- Budget, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-8)
- Board/HUB Meetings: Minutes and Notes, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-9)
- Budget, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-10)
- Balance Sheets and Bank Reconciliation, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-11 to 13-12 (2 folders))
- Financial Statements, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-13)
- Arts Build Communities: Application for Funds, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-14)
- Tennessee Arts Commission Grant Papers, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-15)
- NEA/Roots, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-16)
- Box Office Statements, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-17)
- Touring Calendar, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-18)
- Season Ticket Campaign, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-19)
- Home Season Passes, 1989-1990. (Box-folder 13-20)
- Tennessee for the Arts, 1989-1991. (Box-folder 13-21)
- East Tennessee Foundation, 1989-1991. (Box-folder 13-22)
- Miscellaneous National Endowment for the Arts Correspondence, 1989-1991. (Box-folder 13-23)
- Board Meeting Notes, 1989-1997. (Box-folder 13-24)
- Junior League Follies Advertisements, 1990. (Box-folder 13-25)
- Business Fundraising Campaign, 1990. (Box-folder 13-26)
- Cancelled Destiny--Floor Plan, 1990. (Box-folder 13-27)
- Roots Touring Information, 1990. (Box-folder 13-28)
- TCG Conference, 1990. (Box-folder 13-29)
- Fundraising and Mail List Questions, 1990. (Box-folder 13-30)
- Contributors, 1990. (Box-folder 13-31)
- Membership Drive--Gift Ticket Vouchers, 1990. (Box-folder 13-32)
- Pictures of Nancy and Linda in Nashville, 1990. (Box-folder 13-33)
- Letters, 1990. (Box-folder 13-34)
- Alternative Roots Application Related to National Endowment for the Arts, 1990. (Box-folder 13-35)
- Johnson City Public Schools Contract, 1990. (Box-folder 13-36)
- Arts Advocacy, 1990. (Box-folder 13-37 to 13-38 (2 folders))
- Arts Exchange, 1990. (Box-folder 13-39)
- NEA Dispute, 1990. (Box-folder 13-40)
- Johnson City Various Newspaper Clippings, 1990. (Box-folder 13-41 to 13-42 (2 folders))
- Changes Project Forum Attendees, 1990. (Box-folder 13-43)
- Changes Project--Phase I, 1990. (Box-folder 13-44)
- The Change Project, 1990. (Box-folder 13-45)
- Silent Auction Bids, 1990. (Box-folder 13-46)
- Pertinent Publications for Change, 1990. (Box-folder 14-1)
- Changes Project--Phase II, 1990. (Box-folder 14-2)
- Changes Project--Phase III, 1990. (Box-folder 14-3)
- Changes Project Proposal, 1990. (Box-folder 14-4)
- Changes Project Study Guide, 1990. (Box-folder 14-5)
- Changes Project Business Proposal, 1990. (Box-folder 14-6)
- O-T-R Information, 1990. (Box-folder 14-7)
- Roots Forum, 1990. (Box-folder 14-8)
- Original Grant Proposal, 1990. (Box-folder 14-9)
- The Changes Project, 1990. (Box-folder 14-10 to 14-11 (2 folders))
- Tennessee Humanities Grant Proposal. 1990. (Box-folder 14-12)
- The Changes Project Survey, 1990. (Box-folder 14-13 to 14-15 (3 folders))
- Educational Newspaper Clippings, 1990. (Box-folder 14-16)
- Cancelled Destiny Tour, 1990. (Box-folder 14-17)
- Johnson City Civic Organizations, 1990. (Box-folder 14-18)
- Teacher Packet: "Echoes and Postcards," 1990. (Box-folder 14-19)
- Changes Script and Essays, 1990. (Box-folder 14-20)
- Changes Funding, 1990. (Box-folder 14-21)
- Change in Johnson City Project, 1990. (Box-folder 14-22)
- Teen Pregnancy, 1990. (Box-folder 14-23)
- Teen Theater Fundraising, 1990. (Box-folder 14-24)
- HIV/AIDS Education, 1990. (Box-folder 14-25)
- Changes Rewrites, 1990. (Box-folder 14-26)
- Destiny Cancelled (Script and Prop list), 1990. (Box-folder 14-27)
- A Preacher With a Horse to Ride, 1990. (Box-folder 14-28)
- Artist's Evaluation of the Road Company, 1990. (Box-folder 14-29)
- Theatre Communications Group, 1990. (Box-folder 14-30)
- Appalachian Psychological Conference, 1990. (Box-folder 14-31)
- Arts Center, 1990. (Box-folder 14-32)
- Fever Information, 1990. (Box-folder 14-33)
- The Dream Way Out, 1990. (Box-folder 14-34)
- Art Auction, 1990. (Box-folder 14-35 to 14-36 (2 folders))
- Roots Program, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-1)
- The Hub, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-2)
- Teen Theater, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-3)
- Completed Season, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-4)
- Hub Notes, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-5)
- Arts Build Communities, Applications and guidelines, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-6)
- TAC Partnerships, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-7)
- Statistics, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-8)
- NEA Inter Arts, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-9)
- NEA Theater, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-10)
- Interest Sheets, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-11)
- National Endowment for the Arts: Expansion Arts Program, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-12)
- Budget, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-13)
- Tour Budgets for Goddess and Changes, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-14)
- Database Transactions, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-15)
- Box Office Statements, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-16)
- Pictures from Preacher With a Horse to Ride, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-17)
- Pictures from Goddess, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-18)
- Pictures from Changes, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-19)
- Miscellaneous, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-20)
- Preliminary Audit, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-21)
- Financial Papers and Tax Statements, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-22)
- Miscellaneous Pictures, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-23)
- Plans for use of space in Hannah White Building, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-24)
- Time Forms, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-25)
- NEA/Roots, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-26)
- Tennessee Arts Commission: Grants Applications, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-27 to 15-28 (2 folders))
- Internship--BARD, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-29)
- Volunteer Certificate, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-30)
- 15th Anniversary Season--T-shirts. 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-31)
- Program Advertisements, 1990-1991. (Box-folder 15-32)
- Lila Wallace Places, 1990-1992. (Box-folder 15-33)
- Appalachian Community Fund, 1990-1992. (Box-folder 15-34)
- Audited Financial Statements, 1990-1992. (Box-folder 15-35)
- Virginia Commission for the Arts: Guidelines for Funding, 1990-1992. (Box-folder 15-36)
- Johnson City Public Schools Contracts, 1990-1993. (Box-folder 15-37)
- Visiting Theaters, 1990-1994. (Box-folder 15-38)
- Budgets, 1990-1998. (Box-folder 15-39 to 15-40 (2 folders))
- Plays in Process Nomination, 1991. (Box-folder 16-1)
- Current Touring Proposals, 1991. (Box-folder 16-2)
- Contracts and Miscellaneous, 1991. (Box-folder 16-3)
- Changes Contracts, 1991. (Box-folder 16-4)
- Office Christmas Party, 1991. (Box-folder 16-5)
- Post Office Correspondence, 1991. (Box-folder 16-6)
- Dysfunctions, 1991. (Box-folder 16-7)
- Plays in Process Nomination Forms, 1991. (Box-folder 16-8)
- TAC Government Conference on the Arts, 1991. (Box-folder 16-9)
- Printing Quotes, 1991. (Box-folder 16-10)
- King Springs, 1991. (Box-folder 16-11)
- Leadership 2000, 1991. (Box-folder 16-12)
- Contributors, 1991. (Box-folder 16-13)
- Ind. Fundraising, 1991. (Box-folder 16-14)
- Take this Here and Put it Over There, 1991. (Box-folder 16-15)
- Gallery Information, 1991. (Box-folder 16-16)
- Major Donor Solicitors Training--APEC, 1991. (Box-folder 16-17)
- Focus 2015, 1991. (Box-folder 16-18)
- Goddess Tour Information, 1991. (Box-folder 16-19)
- Changes Script and Technical Setup 1991. (Box-folder 16-20)
- Changes Support, 1991. (Box-folder 16-21)
- Take this Here and Put it Over There, 1991. (Box-folder 16-22)
- Places Miscellaneous. 1991. (Box-folder 16-23 to 16-24 (2 folders))
- Changes Script Progression, 1991. (Box-folder 16-25 to 16-26 (2 folders))
- Interview Release Forms, 1991. (Box-folder 16-27)
- Box Office, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-28)
- Database, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-29)
- Places, Housing materials, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-30)
- Teen Theater Fundraising "Book," 1991. (Box-folder 16-31)
- Conflict Resolution and Mediation Seminar, 1991. (Box-folder 16-32)
- Sexual Pressure Book, 1991. (Box-folder 16-33)
- Theater for Youth Budgets, 1991. (Box-folder 16-34)
- PG 13 Players Information, 1991. (Box-folder 16-35)
- Roots: Artistic Assistance Grant, 1991. (Box-folder 16-36)
- Bank Account, 1991. (Box-folder 16-37)
- A Holiday Evening With Friends, 1991. (Box-folder 16-38)
- AIE Programs, 1991. (Box-folder 16-39)
- The Road Company Newsletter, 1991. (Box-folder 16-40)
- The Christmas Show, 1991. (Box-folder 16-41)
- Ghosts Pictures, 1991. (Box-folder 16-42)
- The Road Company Theater Plans, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-43)
- Insurance Papers, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-44)
- Teen Form Masters, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-45)
- Speak Up Now Theater, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-46)
- TAC, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-47)
- Places and The Displaced Work Reports, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-48)
- Interest Sheets, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 16-49)
- NEA Theater, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-1)
- Rockefeller, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-2)
- Expansion Art, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-3)
- Art Build Communications, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-4)
- Board Minutes and Information, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-5)
- Board Minutes, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-6)
- FY Budgets, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-7)
- Time Forms, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-8)
- Account Function Changes, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-9)
- NEA Inter Arts, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-10)
- Theater Arts Framework, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-11)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-12)
- Program Advertisements, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-13)
- Facility Plan, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-14)
- Program Material, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-15)
- Sun Theater Negatives, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-16)
- National Cultural Alliance, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-17)
- Company of Women, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-18)
- Staffing Notes, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-19)
- Letters, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-20)
- Budget, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-21)
- Rockefeller--Partnerships, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-22)
- The Hub Notes, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-23 to 17-24 (2 folder))
- Silent Art Auction, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-25 to 17-26 (2 folders))
- Season Tickets, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-27)
- United Telephone Exemption Certificate, 1991-1992. (Box-folder 17-28)
- Sun-Model Grant Progress, 1991-1994. (Box-folder 17-29)
- Lynhurst Foundation, 1991-1994. (Box-folder 17-30)
- Christmas Party, 1992. (Box-folder 17-31)
- Census of Service Industries, 1992. (Box-folder 17-32)
- Business Fundraising Campaign, 1992. (Box-folder 17-33)
- Biting the String Snake Contact Interest, 1992. (Box-folder 17-34)
- Biting the String Snake Tour Public Relations, 1992. (Box-folder 17-35)
- The Sun Theater, 1992. (Box-folder 17-36)
- Thank you letters, 1992. (Box-folder 17-37)
- NETCCY, 1992. (Box-folder 17-38)
- Sun Theater Fundraising, 1992. (Box-folder 17-39)
- Teen Pregnancy and Dropout Prevention, 1992. (Box-folder 17-40)
- Grant Follow Up--Speak Up Now, 1992. (Box-folder 17-41)
- Sun Theater Mod Grant, 1992. (Box-folder 17-42)
- Human Race, 1992. (Box-folder 17-43)
- Art Auction Information, 1992. (Box-folder 17-44)
- AIDS Education, 1992. (Box-folder 18-1)
- Artist's Registration Forms, 1992. (Box-folder 18-2)
- Preparing For Russia, 1992. (Box-folder 18-3)
- Budget, 1992. (Box-folder 18-4)
- Audit, 1992. (Box-folder 18-5)
- The Bear Facts Contact Sheets, 1992. (Box-folder 18-6)
- Echoes, 1992. (Box-folder 18-7)
- Office and V Dance, 1992. (Box-folder 18-8)
- Seven Stages Program, 1992. (Box-folder 18-9)
- Spirit of J.C. Award, 1992. (Box-folder 18-10)
- Ghost's Reservations, 1992. (Box-folder 18-11)
- The Hub Organization, 1992. (Box-folder 18-12)
- IRS, 1992. (Box-folder 18-13)
- Insurance, 1992. (Box-folder 18-14)
- Insurance, 1992. (Box-folder 18-15)
- Fire Prevention Inspection, 1992. (Box-folder 18-16)
- Biting the String Snake Miscellaneous, 1992. (Box-folder 18-17)
- Biting the String Snake Short Version, 1992. (Box-folder 18-18)
- Places and The Displaced Information, 1992. (Box-folder 18-19)
- Biting the String Snake Tour Information, 1992. (Box-folder 18-20)
- Biting the String Snake Tour Revision, 1992. (Box-folder 18-21)
- Mailing List and Contacts, 1992. (Box-folder 18-22)
- Listening Project, 1992. (Box-folder 18-23)
- Bite the String Snake, 1992. (Box-folder 18-24)
- Places (Housing Program), 1992. (Box-folder 18-25)
- Places--Phone Bills, 1992. (Box-folder 18-26)
- Charlotte Bennet, 1992. (Box-folder 18-27)
- Bite the String Snake, 1992. (Box-folder 18-28)
- Artists in the Schools, 1992. (Box-folder 18-29)
- Partnership Roundtable Meeting, 1992. (Box-folder 18-30)
- Drumming Workshops, 1992. (Box-folder 18-31)
- Fax Transmissions, 1992. (Box-folder 18-32)
- "Five Hundred Years of the Displaced," 1992. (Box-folder 18-33)
- Ghosts, 1992. (Box-folder 18-34)
- Warg Gregg, 1992. (Box-folder 18-35)
- Valentine's Dance, 1992. (Box-folder 18-36)
- Horsepower, 1992. (Box-folder 18-37)
- Alternative Roots Information, 1992. (Box-folder 18-38)
- God in Little Pieces, 1992. (Box-folder 18-39)
- Bear Facts Information, 1992. (Box-folder 18-40)
- Bear Facts, 1992. (Box-folder 18-41)
- General Mills Foundation, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-42)
- Tax Documents, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-43)
- Miscellaneous, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-44)
- Financial Expenses, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-45)
- "The Fever", 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-46)
- Places Tour Costs, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-47)
- Marvin's Room Audition Development, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-48)
- The Road Company Rag, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-49)
- Speak Up Now: Audora and Echoing, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-50)
- TAC, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 18-51)
- Hub Notes, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-1)
- Budget, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-2)
- Database, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-3)
- Box Office, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-4)
- ACF Sun Theater, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-5)
- New Partnerships, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-6)
- Sun Theater, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-7)
- Levi Strauss--Sun Theater, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-8)
- Hub Notes, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-9)
- Speak Up Now Theater Budget, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-10)
- Program Advertisements, 1992-1993. (Box-folder 19-11)
- Hub Notes, 1992-1994. (Box-folder 19-12)
- Long Term Planning, 1992-1994. (Box-folder 19-13)
- Long Term Plan Reponses, 1992-1994. (Box-folder 19-14)
- Program Advertisements, 1993. (Box-folder 19-15)
- Business Fundraising Campaign, 1993. (Box-folder 19-16)
- The Human Race, 1993. (Box-folder 19-17)
- Industry Fundraising Campaign Letter, 1993. (Box-folder 19-18)
- Leadership 2015 Speech, 1993. (Box-folder 19-19)
- Marvin's Room Reservation and Ticket Records, 1993. (Box-folder 19-20)
- Sam's Wholesale, 1993. (Box-folder 19-21)
- Thank You Notes from Kids, 1993. (Box-folder 19-22)
- Teacher Replies, 1993. (Box-folder 19-23)
- Speak Up Now, 1993. (Box-folder 19-24)
- Art Auction, 1993. (Box-folder 19-25 to 19-27 (3 folders))
- Roots Anthology, 1993. (Box-folder 19-28)
- Rockefeller Final Report Places, 1993. (Box-folder 19-29)
- Still Water, 1993. (Box-folder 19-30)